ICICI Lombard has
taken major steps to increase insurance awareness in Bihar.   The
message of insurance is being conveyed to the people through grassroots campaigns, in collaboration with traffic police and self-help groups.   The
company aims to provide financial security to every individual
and create a safe and empowered environment.
Today, this event is being organised here during the Third Annual State Level
Insurance Committee
and here we, IRDA
officials and Life Insurance Company and General
Insurance Company, make a complete
presentation to the regulator about
what work we have done in Bihar State
regarding both life and non-life awareness,
increasing penetration and
regarding different insurances, in general also regarding health, motor,
SIPs, CSR awareness,
we have presented this completely and
we have received a lot of support
through IRDA officials.  And as I
said earlier, the work we are doing here in
Bihar has been made a model by IRDA for the
entire country
so that this is one such state which has become an
example, a role model that
we have to do such work in other states
like we are working here for insurance.
This is our third annual meeting.  This is the third
annual meeting and we are committed here to be
a lead insurer
and in the last three years significant
improvement has been seen as a regulator they are
getting full support and they are showing their
full commitment in taking insurance
much deeper in the state of Bihar Bihar ko
leke peche plan kya hai
aage That is what I said that the entire
insurance fraternity along with our
regulator we are fully committed into it and
we are and along with the government of Bihar as well we are
getting full support
and you will see a good growth here initially
you know taking it to in the last
[Music]